http://www.fitzpatrickagency.com/privacy-policy

Skip to content
203-438-0404Client Login Search Search Toggle navigation
HomeInsuranceClaims & ServiceCommunity AssociationsBanking ServicesBlogAboutContactPrivacy Policy Fairfield County Bank Insurance ServicesFairfield County Bank Insurance Services, LLC. recognizes your need for privacy and security as you visit our website. Described below are our policies to protect your online privacy.We Do Not Use Cookies On Our WebsiteMany organizations use “cookies” to collect information about those who visit their sites. Fairfield County Bank Insurance Services, LLC. does not use cookies on its website (except as described below). That means you can visit our site without identifying yourself or giving us any information about yourself. We will not obtain any information that identifies you personally unless you choose to provide such information to us.Secured Socket LayerFairfield County Bank Insurance Services, LLC.(FCBIS) designed this website for use with web browsers that use Secured Socket Layer (SSL) technology. Secured Socket Layer is an encryption method that protects the information transmitted between our website and your computer. FCBIS requires that your browser be configured for 128 bit encryption. If your browser is not configured for 128 bit encryption, you can obtain further information about 128 bit encryption from the manufacturer of your browser.Electronic MailOur website contains a form that you can complete and send to us over the Internet. This form requests information about you (such as your address and telephone number). This form is encrypted when it is sent over the Internet which helps protect this information from being intercepted as it is transmitted over the Internet. This is a more secure way of sending us information than sending us general public e-mail. Therefore, we suggest that you always use our e-mail form whenever you wish to send us e-mail. Whenever you communicate with us via Internet e-mail, we will retain the content of the form, the e-mail address and our response. This allows us to maintain an audit trail of our contact and to provide you with the product, service or information you may have requested.Firewalls and RoutersWe use firewalls and routers to create a “doorway” between the Internet and our internal computer network. This doorway restricts access to our internal computer network. Data transmissions that are sent through our firewall and routers to our internal computer network are subject to verification by the firewalls and routers. We are able, thus, to control the data transmissions that gain access to our internal computer network.Changes to Our Privacy PolicyWe may at times change this online privacy policy statement. We might, for example, change our online privacy policy to conform with changes that have been made to state or federal law. Or we might change our online privacy policy so that it conforms with changes made to our website.Reliance on Online Privacy Policy StatementBy displaying this privacy policy statement, we are not modifying any existing written agreements that we have with customers. This privacy policy statement should not be construed as a contract of any kind.If you have any questions or concerns after reading our Privacy Policy Statement, please Contact Us. Get a QuoteGive us some info and we'll get quotes from multiple companies.Get a Quote
Toggle Dropdown AutoHomeownerLifeMotorcycleBusinessMore…Insurance Partners
From Our Blog Don’t Delay — Start Thinking About Winterizing Your RV Today December 6, 2020
10 Things to do to Prepare Your Home for Fall November 6, 2020
10 Easy Renovations That Can Help Prep Your House for Sale October 19, 2020
Connect Online Fairfield County Bank Insurance Services is an independent insurance agency, owned by Fairfield County Bank, with offices in Ridgefield, Stamford, and Fairfield, Connecticut. Give us a call, stop by, or request a quote online to find out how much we can save you on your insurance.HomeAboutContactSitemapRecent Articles Don’t Delay — Start Thinking About Winterizing Your RV Today December 6, 2020
10 Things to do to Prepare Your Home for Fall November 6, 2020
10 Easy Renovations That Can Help Prep Your House for Sale October 19, 2020 Quick LinksAbout UsContact UsService CenterInsurance ProductsGet an Insurance QuoteCompanies We RepresentStaff DirectoryFairfield County BankContact Us 401 Main StRidgefield, CT 06877 203-438-0404 203-431-8789 info [at] fcbins [dot] com info [at] fcbins [dot] com Mon-Fri 8:30am-5pm View all locationsThe insurance products offered by Fairfield County Bank Insurance Services , LLC are not deposits, are not insured by the FDIC, are not guaranteed by the Bank, and are subject to investment risk, including the potential loss of principal invested. © 2020 Fairfield County Bank Insurance Services | Search | Privacy | Disclaimer | Fairfield County Bank | Website by BT
